https://pinconningcheese.com/privacy-policy/

MENUMENUCheeses
Old-Fashioned Pinconning CheesePinconning Cheese CurdsHomemade Cheese SpreadsFlavored Cream Cheese SpreadsString cheesesOther Domestic and Imported CheesesFlavored CheesesSmoked CheesesSwiss CheesesHot & Spicy CheesesLo Salt and Cholesterol CheesesHigh Temperature CheeseAmish Roll Butter
Meats & Fish
Salami, Pepper and Snack SticksSummer SausagesSausage/Hot DogsRing MeatsPickled Meats/ ItemsMichigan made Ham & Other MeatsMichigan Made JerkyFresh Water Smoked Fish
Gifts
Gift Boxes & ItemsT-Shirts & StuffFree Shipping BoxesGift Cards
Fudge & Snacks
Homemade Fudge & CandiesPure Michigan Maple SyrupPinconning HoneyMichigan Made Soda PopsBulk SnacksHomemade Jams & JelliesParamount Gourmet CoffeeSpecialty Crackers and Chips
Condiments
Specialty Spices & Wild Game MixHot Sauces, BBQs, Ketchups, & SalsasSpecialty MustardsMichigan Made Coney-Chili SaucesWorld Famous PizzaloavesHomemade Amish Pasta, Soup MixesPickled MeatsPickles, Olives & More
Deli
Privacy Policy
Conditions of Use By utilizing this site, you agree to all conditions and notices expressed herein. If you do not agree with our conditions of use, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to change the conditions of use at any time. Continued use of the site constitutes your acceptance of any changes made.
Communication
Visiting the site, or sending e-mails to us constitutes electronic communications. You agree to receive electronic communications from us, in the form of e-mail and web site notices. Any agreements, notices, disclosures or other communications procided by us to you electronically satisfy legal requirements for communications to be in writing.
Copyright Policy
All material found at examiner.org is the property of The Pinconning Cheese Company. No materials may be copied, reproduced, republished or distributed in any way unless permission has been granted, and/or a contract has been signed by a representative of The Pinconning Cheese Company.
Violations of this copyright notice will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name contact information including email address demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at general@pinconningcheese.com We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to P.O. Box 926 221 N. Mable St. (M-13) Pinconning, MI 48650-0926.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Pinconning Cheese Co. & Fudge Shoppe - © 2020
